Guide to the Records of the Office of Public Affairs RG.7.3
New York University Archives
Records of the Office of Public Affairs
1927-2015
New York University Archives
New York University. Office of Public Affairs
RG.7.3
71.25 Linear Feet in 23 record cartons, 97 manuscript boxes, one half manuscript box, and one painting.
The Records of the Office of Public Affairs contain the administrative records and subject files of the department as well as university-issued press releases and news clippings regarding university events.
Access Restrictions
Administrative records and unpublished reports of New York University are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation. Access to files spanning multiple years will be opened to researchers based on the date of the most recent materials. Board of Trustees records are closed for 35 years from the date of creation. Materials related to personnel, grievances, job and fellowship searches and applications, and all files that fall under the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) are permanently restricted. Additional restrictions may apply to other materials in this collection. For questions regarding specific restrictions, please contact the University Archives.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred to the University Archives by the Office of Public Affairs over several years. Additional accretions were received in 2016 and 2017; the accession numbers associated with this transfer are 2016.025 and 2017.003.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in four series: Series I: Administrative Files, Series II: Subject Files, Series III: Press Releases, and Series IV: News Clippings. Administrative and subject files are arranged alphabetically. Press releases and newspaper clippings are arranged by date.
Historical Note
The Office of Public Affairs works to support the strategic goals of the university through communication with the external community and the news media. The work of the Office of Public Affairs is aimed at recruiting an exceptional faculty and student body as well as supporting research and teaching goals of the university. The Office of Public Affairs represents all of New York University's (NYU) schools and units, working to emphasize NYU's role as a leading research university, both within New York City and internationally.
Scope and Content
The collection contains administrative records of the Office of Public Affairs, press releases, and news clippings related to the university.
Press releases.; Steinhardt School of Education. Department of Occupational Therapy; Tisch School of the Arts; Brademas, John, 1927-2016; Oliva, L. Jay (Lawrence Jay), 1933-2014
- Series I: Administrative Files, 1975-1986; 2.25 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  Series I contains speeches, correspondence, reports, and publicity materials about the university sesquicentennial (1979-1980) and other events and issues.
  - Conversations for the '80s, 1975-1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Advertising Firms, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Advertising and Publications, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Advertising and Publications, 1980-1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Annual Reports, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bennett's Report to the Faculty, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bennett's Speeches, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bulletin Board Project, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Commencement Speeches, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Education, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Howard Rubenstein Associates, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Jerold Ross Project - Education Programming, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Edward I. Koch Dinner, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Sesquicentennial Advisory Board Meeting, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Annual Reports - President's Letter, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - NYU Printed Material, 1978-1981 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Untitled, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Conference Board: Communicating the Contributions, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Marketing, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Marketing, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Midtown Center Opening, 1979-1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Midtown Center Opening, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - New York City Chancellor's Report, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - New York Alliance for Public Education, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - New York Alliance for Public Education, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Public Affairs Friday Meetings, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Public Affairs Staff Meetings, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Sesquicentennial Advisory Committee Meeting, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Sesquicentennial Commemorative Calendar, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Sesqeuicentenial Executive Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Sesquicentennial Logo, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Sesquicentennial Media Dialogue, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Sesquicentennial General Correspondence, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Sesquicentennial General Correspondence, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Sesquicentennial General Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Sesquicentennial General Correspondence, 1980-1980 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Sesquicentennial General Correspondence, 1980-1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Sesquicentennial General Correspondence, Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Sesquicentennial General Correspondence, Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Sesquicentennial General Correspondene, Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Speechwriters (Freelance), 1980 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Twenty Five W 4th Street, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Urban Studies Center Proposal, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Visitors' Itineraries, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Visitors' Iteraries, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Visitors' Itineraries, 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Visitors' Itineraries, 1979-1979 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Year End Review - NYU Report, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Series II: Subject Files, 1990-1996; 7 Linear Feet
  Series II contains information about campaigns, administrators, government relations, Steinhardt School of Education, Tisch School of the Arts, and other subjects.
  - Albany Day, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Background Material - Briefing Info, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Benefits Committee, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Billion Dollar Campaign - Background, 1992-1995 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Billion Dollar Campaign Background Cont'd, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Billion Dollar Campaign Party, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Billion Dollar Campaign Video, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Blatterfein, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Bluestone, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Brademas (I), 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Brademas (II), 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Brademas (III), 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Brademas (IV), 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Brademas (V), 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Budget Story, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Careers, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Center for Advanced Technology (CAT), 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Center for Advanced Technology (CAT) Digital Multimedia, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Center for War, Peace, and the News Media, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Chubb Scholarship, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - City: Flight To, 1992-1995 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Commencement, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Commencement, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Commissioner Kelly, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Conference Board, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Core Cirriculum, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Development, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Development - Million Dollar Luncheon, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Dime Bank, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Dorms New, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - DWJ, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - EASI, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Education, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Education, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Eighth Street, Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Embezzlement, 1992-1994 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Executive Salaries, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Resource Network, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Ferragamo, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Financial Aid, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Gifts, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Global University Press, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Goldstein, Leon, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Government Relations: Albany Day, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Government Relations: Albany Day, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Government Relations: Albany Day, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Government Relations: Albany Day, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Government Relations: Albany Day, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Government Relations: Albany Day, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Government Relations: CICU, 1992-1995 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Government Relations: DC Trip, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Government Relations: Federal, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Harper's, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Hellenic Conference, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Honorary Degree, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Huang, Dean Alice, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Hunger Conference, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Incident, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Institute of Fine Arts, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Institute of Fine Arts, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Ireland House, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Job Placement, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Job Applicant, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - King Hussein, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - King Hussein Visit, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - La Pietra, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Lax, Peter D. (FAS), 1972-1994 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Medical Center, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Medical Center/Mt Synai (Merger), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Meet the Press Dinner, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Michelangelo, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Middle States Report, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Millenium Brochure, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Minority Faculty Development Grant, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Muhammad, Khallid Abdul, 1988-1994 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Musical Theater, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Musical Theater, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Musical Theater Hall of Fame, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Musical Theater Hall of Fame, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Musical Theater Hall of Fame Coverage, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - National Service Day, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - New Dormitory, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - New Immigrants, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - NYU City, 1991-1994 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - NYU Global 20 Year Report, 1989-1994 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Oliva Briefing, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Oliva Bio, 1990-1994 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Oliva Budget Memo, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Oliva Clips, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Oliva Clips, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Oliva Clips, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Oliva Clips, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Oliva Clips, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Oliva Economic Engine, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Oliva Inaugural, 1991-1994 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Oliva New York Times, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Oliva New York Times Presdients Forum, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Oliva OPED, 1986-1994 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Oliva, L. Jay President, 1980-1993 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Oliva Russian and Russian Program, 1993-1995 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Oliva Sports, 1986-1997 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Oliva Themes, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Oliva Themes, 1993-1996 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Oliva - US News Op-Ed, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Other, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Peters, Frank, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Photo Complaint, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - President L. Jay Oliva, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Provincetown Playhouse, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Public Services I, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Public Services II, 1989-1993 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Public Services/Public Schools, Undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Public Service - Safety Net, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Rectors Conference, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Rectors Conference - Dated Materials, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Rectors Conference - Undated Materials, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Rectors Conference, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Rectors University Bashing, 1990-1993 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Russian Tea Room, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Russian Program, 1991-1996 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Santirocco, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Science, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Schwartz-Chiron, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Education - Riley Visit, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Security, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Statement of Issues, 1983-1994 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Steinhardt - Admin, Leadership, and Technology, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Steinhardt - Applied Psych, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Steinhardt - Art and Art, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Steinhardt - Child and Family Policy Center, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Steinhardt - Culture and Communications, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Steinhardt - Division of Nursing, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Steinhardt - Geriatric Education Center, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Steinhardt - Health Studies, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Steinhardt - Humanities and Social Sciences, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Steinhardt - Immigration and Schooling Conference, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Steinhardt - Institute for Education and Social Policy, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Steinhardt - John A. Hartford Institute of Geriatric Nursing, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Steinhardt - Music and Performing Arts, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Steinhardt - Nutrition, Food Studies, and Public Health, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Steinhardt - NYU Mentions, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Steinhardt - Neil Postman (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Steinhardt - Occupational Therapy, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Steinhardt - Ravitch Diane, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Steinhardt - Teaching and Learning, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Student Health Center, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Student Incidents, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Think Tank, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Think Tank, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Think Tank, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Tisch School of the Arts (I), 2005 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Tisch School of the Arts (II) (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Tisch School of the Arts (III), 2005 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Tisch School of the Arts (IV), 2005 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Tisch School of the Arts (V), 2005 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Tisch School of the Arts (VI), 2005 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Tisch School of the Arts (VII), 2005 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Tisch School of the Arts (I), 2006 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Tisch School of the Arts (II), 2006 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Tisch School of the Arts (III), 2006 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Tisch School of the Arts (IV), 2006 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - UN, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Undergraduate Educations, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - University Pitch, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - VR Project, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Vernon Center, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Vernon, Lillian, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Villa la Pietra, Undated; cuid255; 1 item one watercolor painting (Item RG.7.3_cuid255)
    Artist: R. Steele
    Paintings (visual works)
  - Walker, Arnot (I), 1989 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Walker, Arnot (II), 1989 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Walker, Arnot (III), 1989 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Walker, Arnot (IV), 1989 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Walker, Arnot (V), 1989 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Washington Square Village, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Weehawken Fields, 1992-1995 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Westinghouse Scholar, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Year End Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Soviet Union, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - ABNY-Questionnaire, 1987 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Allocations Report, 1981-1982 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Council: Public Affairs Committee, 1982-1987 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Announcement of Tuition Increase, 1983-1984 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Annual RPT, 1985-1986 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Asbestos, 1987 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Association for a Better New York/Members, 1987 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Brademas Book Advertising, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Brademas Senate, 1985 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Brademas Senate, 1985 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Budgets, 1983-1984 (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Budget: Rough Draft, 1983-1984 (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - Budget Presentation March 1987 (Box 111, Folder 14)
  - Cardinal O'Connor Lecture, 1987 (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - Carter, Arthur L., 1987 (Box 111, Folder 16)
  - Chambers' Statement, 1987 (Box 111, Folder 17)
  - Chancellor's Planning Committee (Subcommittee on Cohesiveness), 1987 (Box 111, Folder 18)
  - Chet Hunter Lecture, 1984 (Box 111, Folder 19)
  - Cohesive Community, 1987-1988 (Box 111, Folder 20)
  - Commencement Information, 1984 (Box 111, Folder 21)
  - Distribution List for Clip Books, 1983 (Box 111, Folder 22)
  - Economics (1), 1988 (Box 111, Folder 23)
  - Economics (2), 1988 (Box 111, Folder 23)
  - E.E.A.A., 1987-1988 (Box 111, Folder 24)
  - Endowments-Chronicle of Higher Education, 1983 (Box 111, Folder 25)
  - $11-$15 Million Anonymous Bequest, 1984 (Box 111, Folder 26)
  - Financial Aid Brochure, 1984 (Box 111, Folder 27)
  - Fund Raising Report, 1982-1983 (Box 111, Folder 28)
  - Gertrude Samuels - Commencement, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 29)
  - GPA, 1988 (Box 111, Folder 30)
  - Hands Around the Park, 1987 (Box 111, Folder 31)
  - "Hot-School" Luncheon, 1987 (Box 111, Folder 32)
  - Image Task Force, 1982-1984 (Box 111, Folder 32)
  - Information Center, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 33)
  - Jacoby/Storms Productions, 1983 (Box 111, Folder 34)
  - JB Trustees Slide Show, 1985 (Box 111, Folder 35)
  - Joint School, 1982-1983 (Box 111, Folder 36)
  - Levine, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 37)
  - NYC College Communicators' Luncheon, 1982-1986 (Box 111, Folder 38)
  - New York Times: Universities Reputations Rankings, 1983 (Box 111, Folder 39)
  - NYU Day in Albany, 1985-1985 (Box 111, Folder 40)
  - NYU Alumni Magazine, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 41)
  - New York University Magazine, 1986-1987 (Box 111, Folder 42)
  - New York Magazine/Brademas, 1984 (Box 111, Folder 43)
  - NYU Magazine Fall Issue, Undated (Box 111, Folder 44)
  - NYU Magazine Fan Mail, 1986-1987 (Box 111, Folder 45)
  - NYU Magazine Mailing List, 1987 (Box 111, Folder 46)
  - Oliva Slide Show: Students, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 47)
  - Orientation Subcommittee, 1987-1988 (Box 111, Folder 48)
  - President's Five Year Report, 1987 (Box 111, Folder 49)
  - President of Portugal Visit: Soares, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 50)
  - Slide Show/Admissions, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 51)
  - Trustees/Senate, 1985 (Box 111, Folder 52)
  - Untitled, 1987-1988 (Box 111, Folder 53)
  - Untitled (1), Undated (Box 111, Folder 54)
  - Untitled (2), Undated (Box 111, Folder 54)
  - UPIC: University Public Issues Committee, 1985 (Box 111, Folder 55)
  - Wesbury Lab (NYU), 1983-1986 (Box 111, Folder 56)
- Series III: Press Releases, 1927-2015; 46 Linear Feet
  Series III contains press releases about NYU sports and other university events and issues.
  - 1927-1929 (Sports) (Box 12)
  - 1930-1931 (Sports) (Box 13)
  - 1931-1933 (Sports) (Box 13b)
  - 1926-1934 (Box 14)
  - 1930-1931 (Box 15)
  - 1931-1932 (Box 16)
  - 1932-1933 (Box 17)
  - May 1933-April 1934, 1933-1934 (Box 18)
  - April 1934-February 1935, 1934-1935 (Box 19)
  - February 1935-October 1935 (Box 20)
  - October 1935-May 1936, 1935-1936 (Box 21)
  - May 1936-January 1937, 1936-1937 (Box 22)
  - January 1937-June 1937 (Box 23)
  - June 1937-March 1938, 1937-1938 (Box 24)
  - March 1938-December 1938 (Box 25)
  - January 1939-December 1939 (Box 26)
  - January 1940-October 1940 (Box 27)
  - October 1940-October 1941, 1940-1941 (Box 28)
  - October 1941-March 1943, 1941-1943 (Box 29)
  - April 1943-February 1944, 1943-1944 (Box 30)
  - February 1944-October 1945, 1944-1945 (Box 31)
  - March 1945-April 1946, 1945-1946 (Box 32)
  - April 1946-February 1947, 1946-1947 (Box 33)
  - March 1947-December 1947 (Box 34)
  - January 1948-June 1948 (Box 35)
  - June 1948-December 1948 (Box 36)
  - January 1949-September 1949 (Box 37)
  - September 1949-March 1950, 1949-1950 (Box 38)
  - March 1950-September 1950 (Box 39)
  - September 1950-April 1951 (Box 40)
  - April 1951-December 1951 (Box 41)
  - January 1952-September 1952 (Box 42)
  - August 1952-December 1952 (Box 43)
  - December 1952-April 1953, 1952-1953 (Box 44)
  - April 1953-October 1953 (Box 45)
  - October 1953-March 1954, 1953-1954 (Box 46)
  - March 1954-August 1954 (Box 47)
  - September 1954-December 1954 (Box 48)
  - January 1955-April 1955 (Box 49)
  - May 1955-September 1955 (Box 50)
  - October 1955-February 1956, 1955-1956 (Box 51)
  - March 1956-June 1956 (Box 52)
  - July 1956-December 1956 (Box 53)
  - January 1957-April 1957 (Box 54)
  - May 1957-September 1957 (Box 55)
  - October 1957-February 1958, 1957-1958 (Box 56)
  - March 1958-November 1958 (Box 57)
  - June 1958-November 1958 (Box 58)
  - January 1958-May 1959 (Box 59)
  - January 1959-September 1959 (Box 60)
  - October 1959-March 1960, 1959-1960 (Box 61)
  - April 1960-September 1960 (Box 62)
  - October 1960-April 1962, 1960-1962 (Box 63)
  - May 1962-December 1962 (Box 64)
  - January 1963-July 1963 (Box 65)
  - August 1963-January 1964, 1963-1964 (Box 66)
  - February 1964-July 1964 (Box 67)
  - August 1964-January 1965, 1964-1965 (Box 68)
  - January 1965-March 1968, 1965-1968 (Box 69)
  - 1968 (Box 70)
  - January 1969-November 1969 (Box 71)
  - December 1969-November 1970, 1969-1970 (Box 72)
  - December 1970-September 1971 (Box 73)
  - October 1971-August 1972, 1971-1972 (Box 74)
  - September 1972-December 1973, 1972-1973 (Box 75)
  - January 1974-April 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 76)
  - April 1975-September 1977, 1975-1977 (Box 77)
  - October 1977-August 1980, 1977-1980 (Box 78)
  - 1979-1982 (Box 112)
  - August 1980-April 1983, 1980-1983 (Box 79)
  - March 1981-December 1983, 1981-1983 (Box 80)
  - April 1983-August 1985, 1983-1985 (Box 81)
  - August 1985-December 1988, 1985-1988 (Box 82)
  - January 1985-January 1990, 1985-1990 (Box 83)
  - September 1986-August 1987, 1986-1987 (Box 126)
  - September 1987-February 1989, 1987-1989 (Box 127)
  - February 1989-September 1989 (Box 84)
  - January 1989-1992 (Box 85)
  - March 1990-September 1990 (Box 86)
  - October 1990-September 1991, 1990-1991 (Box 87)
  - October 1992-March 1995, 1992-1995 (Box 88)
  - March 1996-January 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 89)
  - January 1997-September 1998, 1997-1998 (Box 90)
  - October 1998-June 2000, 1998-2000 (Box 91)
  - June 2000-December 2002, 2000-2002 (Box 92)
  - January 2003-July 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 93)
  - September 2004-August 2005, 2004-2005 (Box 94)
  - September 2008-August 2009, 2008-2009 (Box 95)
  - September 2009-August 2010, 2009-2010 (Box 96)
  - April 1995-February 1996, 1995-1995 (Box 97)
  - September 2005-August 2008, 2005-2008 (Box 98)
  - September 2010-August 2011, 2010-2011 (Box 111A)
  - September 2014-August 2015, 2014-2015 (Box 114)
- Series IV: News Clippings, 1980-2013; 15 Linear Feet
  Series IV contains clippings from various publications about NYU events, issues, and individuals.
  - 1980-1989 (Box 99)
  - 1996-1999 (Box 100)
  - 1985-1986, 2001 (Box 113)
  - 2000 (Box 101)
  - January 2001-October 2001 (Box 102)
  - 1996, 2001 (Box 103)
  - January 2002-February 2003, 2008-2009, 2002-2009 (Box 104)
  - February 2003-August 2003 (Box 105)
  - September 2003-December 2003 (Box 106)
  - January 2004-May 2004 (Box 107)
  - June 2004-July 2004 (Box 108)
  - 2005 (Box 109)
  - 2006 (Box 110)
  - September 2012 -January 2013, 2012-2013 (Box 115)
  - February-May, 2013 (Box 116)
  - June-August 2013 (Box 117)
- Series V: Chronological Files
  - Chronological Files, August 1986-April 1987 (Box 126)